BGM
Never Stop Being an Idol
Don't ever stop being an idol
While wishing for the happiness of your idol
I wish for my idol's happiness, but I also want her to be an idol forever.
It is the ultimate love song
It is the ultimate love song.
After the title of the song
Even if you know that the end will come someday
Please look forward to it
I would like to ask you to announce what you love more deeply than love.
Let's start with Ms. Otani's announcement
A gift of employee muscats from Sashi Haru-san
Don't ever stop!
This is an employee muscat.
I've seen a few pictures here and there on social media this year.
Can you tell us more about it?
That's right, every year Sashiharu-san sends us a lot of delicious Shine Muscats from Oita prefecture.
These are the fruits that make the members work so hard in rehearsals and lessons every day, so please don't stop.
Who among the members eats the most?
We are all very excited to eat them.
It's delicious.
I don't know if I'll ever get used to it.
We all eat each other.
But it's not just for Ikolab.
but also to the Ikomai Joy group.
very generous!
Thank you so much!
It's a perfect gift for summer!
Now, please continue with Mr. Otoshima.
Yes, don't ever stop calling!
When I think of idols, I think of live performances.
I think that the live show is the call of the audience.
When the fans call, the tension of our live performance goes up.
I feel that when the fans call, the tension of the show goes up one more notch.
I'd be really happy if you don't stop your calls for a long, long time.
Do you have any favorite calls for this song?
Yes, I do.
But if you look for it, you can find it in Diamond Lily's impression.
I love the part where they have something to say.
Everyone really gives their best to the calls.
I'd be happy if you could say "Se-no" with me again.
I'd be happy if you could join me in saying "Se-no!
We're going to have a live performance later this month, so I'd love for everyone to join in the calls.
Now, please go on to Ms. Takamatsu.
Yes, I'm definitely not going to stop sticking to it.
What does this mean?
This is about Chiara, one of our members.
Yes, please.
Chiara is a twintail character.
When she had her hair done, she had it redone about 5 times.
She had to have it redone about 5 times.
Five times?
Like, a little more this way.
She was adjusting her hair to the millimeter.
I always thought it was very professional.
Mr. Hare is also very kind in redoing things.
That's right.
Today, he redid it about 5 times.
I'm always standing next to her and watching her do it.
I think it's a wonderful thing, and I hope she doesn't stop doing it.
As a professional twintail artist, this is what I think.
Now let's hear from Ms. Saito.
Don't ever stop twirling!
Kaiten
Conveyor-belt sushi.
I love sushi.
I've been enjoying the fact that I don't get to see sushi revolving these days.
I've loved sushi restaurants since I was a little kid.
I used to see sushi spinning all the time.
I was wondering if they would revolve sushi again.
It's true that these days you can order on a touch panel and have it delivered right away.
But recently, the touch panel is spinning.
What?
So there's a line moving on the monitor.
When you touch it, you can order from there.
That's great.
It's very high-tech, and I like it.
I see.
I love it.
So you'd like the rotation to continue?
Yes, sir.
You'll love it.
Okay, thank you very much.
Next, Mr. Takiwaki, please.
Yes. Don't ever stop our dinner meetings.
What's this about?
It happened recently... with the members, the staff, and Mr. Fingerprints.
We have dinner parties with Fingerprints.
It happens a couple of times a year.
I really enjoy that time.
When we do karaoke or something...
It's really fun to see the staff and the members singing together.
I don't want to quit for the rest of my life.
What do you eat when you go out for dinner?
We usually go out for meat.
When it comes to meat...
Do you have a person in charge of the role or something like that?
Yes, we do.
Thank you for watching.
I didn't really think anything of it.
But it's cute that you never do.
That's cute.
You know...
I was particular about not doing it.
That's where you found your obsession, isn't it?
They really do do other things, don't they?
It's fun to have a fan meeting with everyone.
Please keep doing it!
Please do.
Next, Mr. Sasaki, please continue.
Yes, I'm definitely not going to stop sleeping next to my dog.
What does this mean?
When I go to bed at night and I'm alone in the futon, he scratches the futon and says, "Let me in!
So cute!
Do it.
That's great!
What? Under his armpit.
I thought it was so cute.
So cute.
Yes, it's cute.
It's too cute.
He comes in there every day. He comes in there every day.
But when he wakes up in the morning, he's in a place like his bed.
It's like she's protecting me until I fall asleep.
Maybe she's just trying to be nice to me.
It's very soothing. Thank you very much.
Now then, Mr. Yamamoto, please.
Don't ever stop the hamburger kitchen car.
What's this about?
This is a kitchen car that comes only for the face-to-face meeting events.
I think they are the best burgers in the world.
It's so popular among our members that there's always a long line of people waiting for it during the lunch break.
I drew this picture to express my hope that the staff will continue to support us in the future.
What kind of hamburger is this?
You can choose your own toppings.
You can choose cheese, avocado, and many other ingredients.
Thank you very much.
Can we please not stop eating together? What does this mean?
For some reason, I've recently become addicted to a card game called Uno. I've downloaded the app.
I downloaded the app and was playing with a member the other day. I'm pretty strong.
I'm pretty strong, but I always lose the game.
I introduced this app, but I always lose.
I'm really weak. So can I ask you to get stronger?
I could go on and on.
Are all of you participating in this?
Yes, all of us.
Pastorico and Shobo hand out the cards.
But Mr. Ootani never participates.
Is there a reason for that, Mr. Otani?
I'm the type of person who enjoys watching from the sidelines.
In that sense, I enjoy seeing everyone having fun.
I see.
Thank you very much.
Next, Ms. Noguchi, please.
Yes, definitely don't stop at that point.
Yes.
What is this timing?
I took a cab the other day.
I had to get off at an intersection with a lot of people.
I was flabbergasted and thought, "Oh no, I have to pay quickly.
I was so flustered that I thought I had to pay in a hurry, but he waited for me to open the door until I paid.
It would have been a little embarrassing if I had left the door open.
What if they think I'm in a hurry?
But he waited for me.
The owner of the cab store told me to be careful on my way home.
I thought that was very kind of him.
I thought to myself, "I definitely don't want him to stop at this point.
He didn't open the door first.
It was a kindness that he waited and waited for me.
Kindness.
I hope you will continue to be so kind.
Thank you very much.
Lastly, Mr. Oba, please.
Don't ever stop imitating Sanatun.
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir! What does this mean?
This is Sanah Morohashi, a member of Sanatun.
Sanatun is really good at imitating the members.
They are really good at imitating the members.
It's really fun to watch them do it!
That's why I don't want you to be able to read it.
I'm so glad.
I'm not really doing this for the fans.
I'm not doing this for the fans, I'm just doing it for the members to have fun.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
By the way.
Do you have any favorite mimicry?
My favorite is
I've been doing it a lot lately.
When Kiara eats food.
Yes.
Well, since we're here...
May I?
May I ask you to take care of Oba?
Okay, then.
What if Kiara Saito ate a gingko nut?
If she eats gingko nuts...
I don't eat ginkgo right now.
What if Ms. Saito eats gingko nuts?
Yes, sir.
Yes.
This is beautiful! I'm Hajime Shacho! Bon appétit!
Hey! Delicious!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
This is the best!
How about this, members?
Members, you know what I mean.
Hey!
Mr. Kiawara, it's him.
Myself. May I have him do the survey?
Gingko.
Gingko, please eat some gingko, Mr. Saito.
Yes, sir.
May I? Yes, please.
Eat this.
What?
Out of the blue?
Yeah.
What?
It's been a while.
Try it. Quick.
Bon appétit.
It's good.
How is it?
Is it okay?
If it were her, she'd have said something.
I felt like he was trying hard not to be.
I was a little too conscious.
That's right.
Not at all.
Yes, you're right.
It's delicious.
Yes, it is.
I'll work on it a little more, and I'll see what I can do to make it look a little more like you.
I'll see what I can do.
And I'll look forward to it.
Of course.
I'm looking forward to seeing Alpha's impersonation again.
Thank you very much.